Lenin, like, invented Ukraine and came up with
Ленин типа придумал Украину и придумал
Russian Well, what is there, such a great
русский Ну а что тут тако великий
man was Well, yes, she came
человек был Ну да о столько она
up with so many Nations Bashkorto invented the
придумывала Наций башкорто придумал
Tatars, invented the Tajiks, also
татар придумал ти таджиков тоже
invented no Tajiks, there were this Tajik
придумал нет таджики были этот таджик
again Oh great Andry, today is my
снова О здорово Андрю сегодня у меня
Tajik day, just again, perhaps
день таджиков просто опять чтоли четыре
you are four Tajiks
таджика ты
fourth Come on DAD
четвёртый Да ладно ДАД
only you're the first You're the first I just don't
только ты первый Ты первый Я просто не
understand where the Russians have gone that only
понимаю куда русские делись что одни
Tajiks are
таджики
here I don't know Look, maybe you'll find something else I'll
тут не знаю Поищи может ещё найдёшь
find if there's a fifth it'll be
можно найду если пятый будет это вообще
soon there will be more Tajiks in Russia than
скоро таджиков будет в России больше чем
Russians not on chatroulette probably yes And
русских не в чатрулетке наверное да А
so there are Russians here  anyway, no more without chat
так русских тут всё равно больше без чат
roulette, no more look at the settings,
рулетки не ещё больше смотри настройках
Tajiks like in taxis, Tajiks, Armed Forces, Tajiks
таджики типа в такси таджики ВС таджики
and Russians only
а русские только
drink, they don’t drink, they don’t drink, they don’t just drink, they do
бухают не
n’t
не бухают не бухают не только бухают не
Why do they drink, they have the right to also
Почему бухают бухают имеют право ещё и
work, they do a lot of things, and today,
работают да Много чего делают Да сегодня
today, what else are we talking about?  I see that, for
сегодня вообще о чём ещё я смотрю что
example, among Tajiks there are no
вот например э среди таджиков нет
unemployed in Russia, but among Russians
безработных в России а среди русских
there are. How does this
есть Как так
happen?
получается Не
I don’t know. Maybe they’re just drunk or right,
знаю Может они просто пяные л право
probably yes. No no
наверное да Нет нет
No. I’ll tell you, as a Tajik who
Нет я скажу тебе как таджик который
arrived in 2002, probably the difference between
приехал в 2002 году наверное отличие
Tajiks and local aborigines
таджиков от местных аборигенов
seems to me  that they didn’t honu didn’t
мне кажется что они не хону не
grab it, so probably I dare to
хапанула поэтому наверное Осмелюсь
assume that among the aborigines there are
предположить что среди аборигенов есть
unemployed people, the same thing And in Tajikistan
безработные тоже самое И в Таджикистане
there are kids who don’t work,
есть ребятки которые не работают
for example,
например
di na she, well, in my opinion, they are rare,
ди на ше ну их правда по-моему редко
probably Well, I haven’t been there in Tajikistan for a long time,
наверное Ну я давно там в Таджикистане
really. And you’re in Volgograd  you live
не бывал правда А ты в Волгограде живешь
in the Volgograd region And by
да область Волгоградской А по
nationality are you Tajik or not yes yes
национальности ты таджик или нет да да
Tajik it makes sense for me to hang up a Tajik flag it makes sense for me to hang up a
таджик смысл мне вешать таджикский флаг
female flag and it makes sense for you to hang up a Russian flag it’s
смысл мне вешать жеский ла а смысл тебе
not Russian, it’s not
русский вешать не это российский не
Russian, you know it perfectly from the Russians That’s
русский великолепно знаешь у русских Вот
right, you see there’s a Tajik flag and there’s a Russian one
именно видишь таджикский есть а русского
No, well, here again  Russian
Нет ну опять же вот у русских
nationalists have an imperial flag, they
националистов имперский флаг они Её
call it, well, more precisely, they call it a flag. Not not
называют ну его точнее флаг называют Не
all. Not all of them. Someone
не все Не все они кто-то Имперский
is pulling the Imperial flag. Someone else is pulling someone from
тягает кто-то ещё какие-то кто-то
Vlasov. By the way, the Russians,
власовский вот кстати вот у русских
look, the Tajiks have their own territory.
смотри у таджиков есть своя территория
Yes, the Kazakhs have it.  Bashkortos have Tatars
Да у казахов есть у башкорто есть татар
everywhere It’s clear Where is which republic And the
всюду Понятно Где какая республика А у
Russians don’t even have their own
русских нет даже своей
republic and what’s wrong with that Well, it’s not
республики и что в этом такого Ну не
just Russians in Russia, it’s like yes, that
просто русские в России это как да то
is, uh,
есть ээ
yes, they don’t have their own
да у них нету своей
republic And where is the Russian republic, well,
республики А где русская республика ну
if there is no Russian Republic, that’s stupid
если нету русской Республики это глупи
Sika is complete damn in the United States of
Сика полнейшая блин в Соединённых Штатах
America I’ll draw an analogy there is no
Америки аналогию проведу нету
American not so No the point is that
американской не так Нет дело в том что
no so look at in the United States of
нет так смотрите в в Соединённых Штатах
America there is no de that is the American
Америки нету де то есть там американская
nation there is still the same as the Australian
нация всё так же как австралийца
artificial Yes artificial And all the nations are
искуственная Да искусственно А все нации
artificial you won’t
искусственные не
believe all the nations are artificial  not
поверите все нации искусственные не
artificially created I mean all
искусственно созданные Я имею в виду все
nations are artificially created not Why
нации искусственно созданы не Почему
Russians for example historically formed
русские например исторически сложившиеся
Tajiks historically formed Ubeks
таджики исторически сложившиеся убеки
historically Add up Russian artificially
исторически Сложи рус искусственно
created
созданная
nation by Lenin Stalin what Show
нация ленином Сталиным какие Покажите
me some Russians in the 10th century and in the
мне каких-то русских в X веке и в
census of Russians in the 10th century
переписи населения руских в X веке
there are no Russians  not a population census, a
никаких руских не не переписи населения
population census of the 19th century, I won’t say,
переписи населения XIX века я не скажу
but in the census, for example, from the
но в переписи например николаевских
time of Nicholas II, there were Great Russians Little Russians, there
времён второго были великороссы малорос
were no Russians, there were no Gypsies, I don’t know there
никаких русских не было циган не знаю
were no Russians,
русских не было
well, there weren’t and there weren’t, let’s say there were Poles,
Ну ну не было и не было допустим поляки
there were Jews, yes there were
были евреи были
Russians. Well, they called themselves Great Russians.
да русски Ну они великороссы себя
We
называли ве ещ Кто были великороссы мы
no longer know and will not recognize who the Great Russians were, but there were no Russians. The Russians were
уже не знаем и не узнаем но русских не
invented in the 20th century by Lenin
было русских придумали в XX веке Ленин
and
со
Stalin as the Ukrainian Ukraine. Yes,
сталином как Украину ную Украину Да
Lenin, like, invented Ukraine and invented
Ленин типа придумал Украину и придумал
the Russian. Well, what was the great man? Well,
русский Ну а что великий человек был Ну
she invented so many nations.
да о столько она придумывал Наций
Bashkortos invented them.  Tatars invented ty
башкорто придумал татар придумал ти
Tajiks also
таджиков тоже
invented no Tajiks were by the way now
придумал нет таджики были кстати сейчас
advertising is not before
реклама не до это
this before this before this you were considered
это до этого до этого вас считали там
some kind of Persians there and all that you are
какими-то персами и всё что вы от
no different from Iranians But it is
иранцев не отличаетесь А вот именно
Lenin who is different Lenin created the Tajik Socialist
Ленин отличаемся Ленин создал таджикскую
Republic Yes, and they sort of singled out Tajik
СР Да и типа выделили таджикский
nationalism  they did and that’s it
национализм сделали да и всё
Yes, nationalism exists everywhere
Да национализм он же везде существует
You are, you and the Iranians were one people
Вот вы вы ж вы ж с иранца один народ
True Well, once upon a time there were one
Правда Ну когда-то да когда-то были один
people Yes, and then Lenin came up with
народ Да а потом Ленин придумал отдельно
Tajiks separately, Russians separately,
таджиков отдельно русских отдельно
Ukrainians separately, he invented 15 republics and then
украинцев 15 республик придумал а потом
another  in the middle of Russia began to invent
ещё в середине России начал придумывать
not 15 not 15 15 12 not 15 as a result 15
не 15 не 15 15 12 не 15 в результате 15
came up with not Well, the Baltic
придумал не А ну ти прибалтийские
Republics Stalin Yes Stalin yes Yes
Республики Сталин Да Сталин да Да
invented No the point is that Lenin Look,
придумал Нет дело в том что Ленин Смотри
this was still Lenin’s project Lenin
это ещё был проект Ленина Ленин их
came up with them, there was simply no political
придумал просто не было политической
will to implement them  Stalin implemented it and
воли реализовать Сталин реализовал а
Lenin came up with it. Well, from a history course. As if Lenin
Ленин Ну из курс истории Как бы Ленин
were not the emperor, so that he personally
это не был императором чтобы он лично
invents it, no, the emperor will not
придумывал нет так император не
invent it; the emperor rules the empire;
придумает император он правит империи
well, I mean that the role of the individual
есть Ну я имею в виду что роль личности
in history, of course, is great. The fact is
в истории конечно она велика Дело в том
that, well, such a country  how Tajikistan
что ну такой страны как Таджикистан не
didn’t really exist before
было ж правда до
Lenin, yes yes, that is, it turns out that Lenin
Ленина да да то есть получается Ленин
invented Tajikistan Well, Lenin invented
придумал таджи Ну Ленин придумал
Tajikistan Well, let it be so, let it
Таджикистан Ну пусть пусть так пусть так
be good Lenin invented
будет хорошо Ленин придумал
Tajikistan It’s interesting, it just turns out uh,
Таджикистан Интересно просто получается
if you look at Russian cities like this,
ээ вот если так смотреть как русский
for example, uh if Firdousi Yes, that’s
города например ээ если Фирдоуси Да вот
him  was not a Tajik, it’s true because
он же не был таджиком правда потому что
Lenin came up with Tajiks only in the 20th century
Ленин придумал таджиков только в XX веке
in the context of today’s
в контекст в контексте сегодняшнего
understanding
понимания
of Tajiks Maybe but This
таджиков Может быть но Этот
representative of the Tajik group
представитель таджикской на группы
The question is: Do you think Prince
Вопрос вот Как вы считаете князь
Vladimir was a
Владимир был
Ukrainian in the context of modern
украинцем в контексте современного
understanding Well, considering the fact that he
понимания Ну учитывая то что он из
came from Novgorod no  From which Novgorod
Новгорода вышел нет С какого Новгорода
did he come from his Pope? Not he was
вышел он вышел из своего Пап Не он в
born in Kiev, I mean that Ladoga
Киеве родился я имею в виду что Ладога
Ladoga once again Which Ladoga he was born in Kiev
Ладога ещё раз Какая Ладога он в Киеве
Vladimir the Baptist Yes, that's right,
родился Владимир креститель Да правильно
from dad Svetoslav from Ladoga No he has a
от папы светослава из ладоги Нет у него
pa No he Vladimirsky ky no again
па Нет он Владимирский кь нет ещ раз
in  Kiev, look Now I’m opening
в Киеве посмотри Сейчас открываю
Wikipedia Yes, well, he was born in Kiev if
Википедию Да ну Родился он в Киеве если
Well, in the context of today,
Ну в контексте сегодняшнего времени
let a Ukrainian be a Ukrainian,
пусть будет украинцем украинец вот не
I’m not interested, it’s just how you Tajiks
мне интересно просто вот как вы таджики
living in the Russian Federation understand,
живущие в Российской Федерации понимаете
no stop stop Andrey are not Tajiks I
нене стоп стоп Андрей не таджики Я
’m you’re a Tajik in the Russian Federation
я вот вы таджик в Российской Федерации
like that  how do you perceive our history? Yes,
так как вы воспринимаете нашу историю Да
Ukrainian yes. That is, you
украинскую да То есть вы
understand, yes in the context. That is,
понимаете да в контексте То есть
it turns out Prince Vladimir. Yes,
получается князь Владимир Да он
in the modern context, he is like a Ukrainian,
в современном контексте это как украинец
not like a Russian. Well, if we take the fact that Kiev
не как русски Ну если брать то что Киев
is the current capital of Ukraine, then let it
- это нынешняя столица Украины то пусть
be good for the Ukrainians, that is, it
будет украинцам хорошо то есть
turns out  I don’t feel sorry, but the Russians don’t
получается мне не жалко да россияне не
have a relationship with Prince Vladimir, the
имеют к князю Владимиру отношения
Ukrainians do, the Russians don’t have
украинцы имеют россияне не имеет
it right once again in the context of the fact
правильно ещё раз ещё раз в контексте
that he was born in Kiev and Kiev
того что Родился он в Киеве а Киев нынче
is now Ukraine, that’s all I understand, since it’s super,
это Украина то да всё Поня так как супер
let it be so, super Russians,
пусть пусть будет так так супер россияне
you see, okay  what do you understand
видь хорошо что вот вы понимаете потому
because the Russians don’t understand something, they are
что русские они не понимают они что-то
starting to lay claim to our
начинаю раз претендовать на на нашего
Prince Vladimir, to our princes who
князя Владимира на наших князей которые
ruled them there, including the fact
правили там ими в том числе Дело в том
that our princes They were such
что наши князья Они были такими
occupiers, they seized a
оккупантами они там захватывали на этих
lot of land in these swamps  they made some kind of
болотах куча земель делали какие-то
fortresses and collected tribute from the Finno-
крепости и собирались них дань с фино
Ugric peoples of different peoples, and the Russians are
угорских разных народов а россияне те
exactly where Moscow is now. The Slavs didn’t
тно где сейчас Москва там славяне Не
live there. And who lived there?
жили А кто там жил
Pig Mountain
свиногорье
Moscow when they just made it in the 10th century,
Москву когда сделали просто вот в X веке
for example, or on the territory of the
на пример вот или на территории вот
Volgograd region. If we take that  it’s
Волгоградской области Если брать то тут
as if the Sarmatians lived there No there there not if
как бы сарматы жили Нет там там не если
the Bulgars for example the Volga lived the current
Булгары например Волжские жили нынешних
Tatars Yes the thing is the Tomsk Bulgars are not
татар Да дело дело в томские Булгары не
Tata but the Chuvash Chuvash more well the ancestors the
Тата а чуваший чуваший больше ну предки
ancestors speak correctly after all Yes
предки правильно говорить вс-таки Да
because again if in the context of the
потому что опять же если в контексте
language for example the Russian language
например взять языка то русский язык
The current and then Russian language is
нынешний и тогдашний русский язык - это
not the same thing from the point of view of grammar
не одно и тоже с точки зрения грамматики
and
там и
other things. Let all languages ​​be
прочего Пусть будет все языки они
artificial. For that matter, I just
искусственные Коль на то пошло Просто я
mean that in the context of today's
имею в виду что в контексте сегодняшнего
Russian they would not understand perhaps the
времени рус они не поняли бы возможно
Russians who lived in the same  there century
русских которые жили в том же там веке
because the grammatical norms were
потому что грамматически нормы были
different in the context, it’s necessary to take it,
другие в контексте обязательно брать
I’ll say more, look when we
нужно я больше скажу смотрите когда мы
take it, we open the chronicles of the Kievan
берём открываем летописи так Киевского
time in Russia and we read, we see the
времени на Руси и мы читаем мы видим те
same Ukrainian words by sound. Following the
же украинские слова по звучанию По
example when the Russian Bert for them
примеру когда русский Берт для них
this
этой
Yes, why are there translations  I don’t mean
Да почему существуют переводы не имею в
that we can type vi For example, the
виду что мы можем типа ви Вот например
prince of the prince was called in the chronicles not
князь князя звали в летописях не
Vladimir but Volodymyr Volodymyr, just
Владимир а володимир володимир так же
like in the Ukrainian language
как в украинском языке
Volodymyr and in the Russian language Vladimir not And the
володимир а в русском языке Владимир не
world is the world And as the world in Ukrainian will be
А мир мир А как мир на украинском будет
light of
свет
suites
свит
look No look there is if  you
смотри Нет смотри есть если ты
look
посмотришь
Tolstoy had War and peace you know before
У толстого было Война и мир знаешь до
the reform of the Russian language there was
реформы языка русского была в русском
a letter and a dot in the Russian language like in
языке буква и точечка такая как в
Ukraine Uh-huh And for example the word peace
Украине Угу И вот например слово мир
with a dot and the word peace with that These
через точку и слово мир через такую Это
two different words
разные два слова
were like peace not War and peace like peace  Well,
были как мир не Война и мир как мир Ну
the world is like a planet, like a universe, but
мир это как планета как как вселенная но
I’m talking about the Ukrainian language once again, I’m talking about the
я про украинский язык ещё раз я про
Ukrainian language. From the Ukrainian language, the world is
украинский язык с украинского языка мир
translated as light of suites. No There is,
переводится как свет свит Нет Есть есть
look in Ukrainian and Myr.
смотри в украинской и мыр Я Сим миром
world We
слово Там мы зибрали всем миром Мы
gathered with the whole world, as it were, and
собрались всем миром как бы вот и
did something like this synonymous words are,
сделали типа эту синонимичные слова это
well, it’s not that they’re synonymous, they’re
ну это не то что синонимичные это
homonymous Synonyms are those that have the
омонимичные Синонимы - это те что имеют
same meaning homonyms homonyms
одинаковое значение омонимы омонимы
that have the same meaning key key key
которые одинаково зча лю ключ ключ ключ
world and world world these are homonyms world world Well
мир и мир мир это омонимы мир мир Ну
key  the key
ключ ключ
sounds the same this is a Synonyms this
звучит одинаково это а Синонимы это
For example When we have
Например Когда у нас
uh two words sound different But one
ээ два слова по-разному звучат Но одно
means
означает
Well close close minded for example
Ну близкий недалёкий например
a little bit but through through not not not a
немножко но через через не не не
little bit it's not a little bit we don't write with because
немножко это не немножко не пишем с пото
not it's not a synonym You know why
что не это не синоним Знаешь почему
Because close  - it’s not a fact that
Потому что недалёкий - это не факт что
it’s close. Why
близкий Ну почему
can there be a whole gradation between close and distant,
между близким и далёким может быть ещё
for example,
целая градация например
white and not black, for example, between
вот белый и не чёрный например между
white and black there’s a lot of other things? Yes, it’s not
белым и чёрным ещё куча всего есть Да не
not black, it can be green,
не чёрный он может быть зелёный
that’s right. Well, that’s how it is, close and
правильно Ну вот та так и тут близкий и
close  maybe there is close there is
недалёкий может быть есть близкий есть
distant there is average truth from the
далёкий есть средний правда с точки
point of view of Russian spelling that’s when we
зрения русской орфографии вот когда мы
write for example yes right there close we
пишем например да тут же недалёкий мы
can write together because it can be
можем писать слитном потому что можно
replaced with a synonym close It’s not a fact that
заменить синонимом близкий Не факт что
close is a rule Russian is not an adjective
близкий правило русское не прилагатель
we can replace not a synonym we can
мы можем заменить не синоним мы можем
simply replace  in other words, not
заменить просто другим словом не
necessarily close de in that don’t
обязательно близкий де в том что не
look I live not far from
смотрите Я живу недалеко от
the store this does not mean that I live
магазина это это не значит что я живу
close to the
близко к
store in the sense of Odin because there
магазину по смыслу Одина по потому что
is no There is a concept close far and there
нет Есть понятие близко далеко а ещё
is also for example
есть например
enough for example there are a bunch of different words
достаточно например ещё куча разных слов
there are that are not  close and not far
есть которые не близко и недалеко
relatively enough It's enough -
относительно достаточно Это достаточно -
It's not a synonym for the word not far That's exactly
Это не синоним слова недалеко Вот именно
what I mean I'm explaining that
что я Я же объясняю что
uh not far and close are different
ээ недалеко и близко - это разные
concepts they're not synonyms I understand that is,
понятия это не синонимы у понял то есть
not everything that's not far away Is close like that
не всё что не далеко Есть близко вот так
Well it's relative Yes it's relative
Ну это относительно Да относительное
the concept depends, again, in what kind of profession you are,
понятие смотря опять же в каком ко вы
who by
кто по
profession I work as a teacher of the Russian
профессии я учителем работаю русского
language of literature
языка литературы
Cool And what did you
Прикольно А что
graduate from? Well, this is not a core
заканчивали Ну это не профильная мо
specialization But what about you, a Russian language
специализация А как же вы русский язык
teacher qualified
препода квалифицировал
qualified Well, what ends up
квалифицировал Ну что заканчивается
a person with a higher education with a higher education
человек с высшим с высшим образованием
can undergo retraining Well,
может пройти переквалификацию Ну
engineering  direction I can’t help but
инженерное направление у меня не
call myself an
поворачивается язык назвать себя
engineer If you don’t have a
инженер Если у вас нету образования
pedagogical education or how can you do
педагогического или там как вы можете
Russian language and literature in the Russian
русский язык литературу в Российской
Federation, you can do this by
Федерации это можно сделать пройти
retraining and teaching, that is,
переквалификацию и преподавать то есть
to be a physicist, but by retraining
быть физиком но пройти переквалификацию
and teaching Russian language and literature,
и преподаватель руский язык и литературу
I’m not a physicist  I’m not a physicist, an engineer, I’m
не я не физик я не физик инженер у меня
qualified as an
квалификация
engineer, how long does it take to retrain?
инженер инженер сколько переквалификация
Well, for example, if you
проходит Ну я например если так по
take it like that, I studied for about a year, well, that
времени брать учился порядка Ну года а
is, I understood, that is, in a year you
то есть понял то есть за год из инженера
can turn an engineer into a teacher of Russian
можно сделать преподавателя русского
language and literature, a teacher, a teacher, a
языка и литературы учителя учителя
teacher, He works at a university,
преподаватель Он работает в университете
I  I understand, and he’s a teacher at school. It’s interesting, that is,
я понял а учитель он в школе интересно
it turns out. What
то есть получается
happens is that in a year you can raise the base from scratch;
Что получается что за год можно с нуля
for you, there was no pedagogical base;
для вас же не было педагогической базы
just within a year, you
оден как раз таки в течение года ты
have a higher education. Yes,
обладаешь обладая высшим образованием Да
but I’ll repeat myself; I’m the top I don’t consider it
но я повторюсь я верхним Я не считаю это
higher  Education regarding me at the
высшим образованием относительно меня в
university, general disciplines are studied,
университете изучаются общие дисциплины
the same psychology that is studied in pedagogy,
та же психология которая в педагогике
for example, don’t look, I’ll say
изучается например да не смотри я скажу
this, a person who studies Russian
так человек который учится на русский
language and literature, anyway, he has 5 years,
язык и литературу всё равно у него 5 лет
he has 5 years, subjects that you
есть есть у него 5 лет предметы которые
can’t learn in a year
за год не из учишь
without  Well, maybe it’s not possible And yes That’s how it is
без Ну возможно не возможно А да Так оно
But nevertheless, is it physically possible
и есть Вот Но тем не менее физически ли
if you have Yes yes I agree
если у тебя Да да Согласен
completely, it’s impossible to read all the literature for
полностью всю литературу невозможно
that matter, even live 80
прочитать ль на то пошло даже проживи 80
years in the Russian Federation If
лет вот в Российской Федерации Если у
you have a higher education, not a
тебя есть высшее образование не
purchased diploma, but  after all, it
купленный диплом а всё-таки
really is confirmed by the university. Well, you
действительно подтверждает ВУЗ Вот то ты
have the right to undergo requalification, this is
имеешь право пройти переквалификацию это
quite legal, accordingly, if for
вполне законно соответственно если
example, for a certain
например ты в течение там определённого
amount of time you will undergo uh
количества времени будешь проходить ээ
certain how to say this, oh my God,
определённые как это сказать-то господи
well, re-examination, so let’s say Yes,
э ну переэкзаменовка так скажем Да
retraining also during work, that’s why it’s
переподготовку тоже в течение работы вот
normal  quite a phenomenon, a
поэтому нормальное вполне явление
legitimate legitimate phenomenon. That is,
законное законное явление То есть
it turns out that
получается что
uh, Any person who, for example, was a
ээ Любой человек который например был
physicist, a chemist, and so on, can
там физиком химикам и так далее да может
undergo retraining and teach this in a year. Yes, I do
пройти переквалификацию и за год
n’t know what’s wrong with that, but it seems to me that
этом такого не знаю мне кажется как-то а
programming can be done in a year.  I do
программирование можно за год тоже так
n’t know how to teach either I don’t know I haven’t studied
преподавать не знаю не знаю не изучал
programming That is, this It only
программирование То есть это Это только
works with this
работает с этим
with the Russian language and
с русским языком и
literature I don’t know maybe it’s the
литературой не знаю может быть и с
same system with mathematics and
математикой такая же система и с физикой
maybe the same system with physics it’s
может быть такая же система
quite possible to retrain from psychology and mathematics already cool
математику прикольно вполне возможно Да
What's so interesting about this? It's
что в этом
interesting how many years have you been
такое Интересно а сколько лет вы уже
teaching Russian language and literature?
преподаёте русский язык и литературу
Less than 10 years
менее 10 лет
cool. Uh-huh. Do
прикольно
you have any question? Yes no question no?
Угу У вас какой-то Вопрос есть да нет
Sign up on Mi Telegram right for him
нету пидпись на Mi Telegram прям за он
AK more and more respectfully YouTube keeping
АК це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
us busy through srr  in the new ban and duzhe there is a lot of
нас через срр в ньй бан и дуже багато
video I don’t show people right now I don’t show
вдео не показую людям вчасно не показуе
information about ST for this purpose so that we can
информация про СТ тому для того щоб ми
write Mali operational link right
Мали оперативный звязок пишиться прямо
away and while there in telegra okm video
зараз а пок там в телегра окм видео ще
shtezh va and korisna information and we are guilty of
теж ва и корисна информация и мы повинни
you trimati postiyny operational
з вами тримати постийний оперативный
link
звязок
independent  I'll show you about it
незалежно в того чи покаже вам про це
YouTube Glory to Ukraine letter
YouTube Слава украини пись